{
  "type": "quiz",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "ガ",
      "answer": "ga"
    },
    {
      "question": "ギ",
      "answer": "gi"
    },
    {
      "question": "グ",
      "answer": "gu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゲ",
      "answer": "ge"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゴ",
      "answer": "go"
    },
    {
      "question": "ザ",
      "answer": "za"
    },
    {
      "question": "ジ",
      "answer": "ji"
    },
    {
      "question": "ズ",
      "answer": "zu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゼ",
      "answer": "ze"
    },
    {
      "question": "ゾ",
      "answer": "zo"
    },
    {
      "question": "ダ",
      "answer": "da"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヂ",
      "answer": "ji"
    },
    {
      "question": "ヅ",
      "answer": "zu"
    },
    {
      "question": "デ",
      "answer": "de"
    },
    {
      "question": "ド",
      "answer": "do"
    },
    {
      "question": "バ",
      "answer": "ba"
    },
    {
      "question": "ビ",
      "answer": "bi"
    },
    {
      "question": "ブ",
      "answer": "bu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ベ",
      "answer": "be"
    },
    {
      "question": "ボ",
      "answer": "bo"
    },
    {
      "question": "パ",
      "answer": "pa"
    },
    {
      "question": "ピ",
      "answer": "pi"
    },
    {
      "question": "プ",
      "answer": "pu"
    },
    {
      "question": "ペ",
      "answer": "pe"
    },
    {
      "question": "ポ",
      "answer": "po"
    }
  ]
}
